Guide to the American Society of Planning Officials Records, 1925-1982
American Society of Planning Officials Records, 1925-1982
- Series VI. ASPO honorary life members files
  - Honorary Life Member #147 - Ives, Richard (Box 30, Folder 60)
  - Honorary Life Member #148 - Johnson, Waldemar C. (Box 30, Folder 61)
  - Honorary Life Member #135 - Johnston, David A. (Box 30, Folder 62)
  - Honorary Life Member #158 - Kayanan, Antonio C. (Box 30, Folder 63)
  - Honorary Life Member #167 - Kelly, Burnham (Box 30, Folder 64)
  - Honorary Life Member # 61 - Kennedy, G. Donald (Box 30, Folder 65)
  - Honorary Life Member # 163 - Keyes, Scott (Box 30, Folder 66)
  - Honorary Life Member #159 - Klove, Robert C. (Box 30, Folder 67)
  - Honorary Life Member #129 - Koenigsberger, Otto H. (Box 30, Folder 68)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Kramer, Ferd (Box 30, Folder 69)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Kreinberg, Joseph S. (Box 30, Folder 70)
  - Honorary Life Member #62 - Krieger, Elmer (Box 30, Folder 71)
  - Honorary Life Member #18 - Kuehne, Hugo Franz (Box 30, Folder 72)
  - Honorary Life Member #182 - Labatut, Jean (Box 30, Folder 73)
  - Honorary Life Member #115 - LeBaron, Olin W. (Box 30, Folder 74)
  - Honorary Life Member #117 - Leipziger-Pearce, Hugo (Box 30, Folder 75)
  - Honorary Life Member #33 - Logan, Leonard M. (Box 30, Folder 76)
  - Honorary Life Member #176 - Ludlow, William H. (Box 30, Folder 77)
  - Honorary Life Member #112 - Mackelmann, D.E. (Box 30, Folder 78)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Malley, Frank H. (Box 30, Folder 79)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - McCormick, Thomas E. (Box 30, Folder 80)
  - Honorary Life Member #70 - Menhinick, Howard K. (Box 30, Folder 81)
  - Honorary Life Member #66 - Merrill, Harold A. (Box 30, Folder 82)
  - Honorary Life Member #114 - Miller, Harold W. (Box 30, Folder 83)
  - Honorary Life Member #136 - Miller, J. Marshall (Box 30, Folder 84)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Miller, Willis H. (Dr.) (Box 30, Folder 85)
  - Honorary Life Member #92 - Mitchell, Robert B. (Box 30, Folder 86)
  - Honorary Life Member #164 - Moore, Lawrence (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Honorary Life Member #53 - Morrow, C. Earl (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Honorary Life Member # 138 - Mueller, Elmer E. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Honorary Life Member #127 - Nolen, John, Jr. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Honorary Life Member #122 - Norton, Charles McKim (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Honorary Life Member #74 - Orton, Lawrence M. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Honorary Life Member #11 - Osborne, Harold S. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Honorary Life Member #149 - Parker, John A. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Parks, Warren W. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Honorary Life Member #42 - Pelletier, Burroughs (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Honorary Life Member #173 - Pico, Rafael (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Life Member #116 - Ratcliff, Richard U. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Life Member #146 - Reid, Paul M. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Honorary Life Member #118 - Ridings, Willard A. (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Honorary Life Member #120 - Roemer, Armin A. (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Honorary Life Member #140 - Scheftell, Bernard H. (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Honorary Life Member #139 - Schellie, Kenneth L. (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Honorary Life Member #106 - Schocken, Thomas D. (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Scott, Mellier G., Jr. (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Honorary Life Member #37 - Segoe, Ladislas (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Honorary Life Member #165 - Shefelman, Harold S. (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Honorary Life Member #190 - Shope, John H. (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Life Member #152 - Simmons, Kenneth B. (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - Honorary Life Member #57 - Smutz, Huber Earl (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - Honorary Life Member #45 - Somerville, James G. (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - Honorary Life Member #179 - Spangle, William E., Jr. (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - Honorary Life Member #151 - Starick, Herbert W. (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Honorary Life Member #20 - Stearns, Frank F. (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Honorary Life Member #133 - Stebbins, C. Rowland (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - Honorary Life Member #132 - Stellhorn, Arthur K. (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - Honorary Life Member #184 - Sutermeister, Oscar (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - Honorary Life Member #141 - Swartzel, A. Dean (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - Honorary Life Member #128 - Teare, Wallace G. (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - Honorary Life Member #90 - Thiry, Paul (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Honorary Life Member #187 - Thrift, Eric W. (Box 31, Folder 35)
  - Honorary Life Member #93 - Tuemmler, Fred W. (Box 31, Folder 36)
  - Honorary Life Member #119 - Vance, John E. (Box 31, Folder 37)
  - Honorary Life Member #99 - Villalobos, Julio (Box 31, Folder 38)
  - Honorary Life Member #166 - Waechter, Heinrich H. (Box 31, Folder 39)
  - Honorary Life Member #49 - Wallace, John (Box 31, Folder 40)
  - Honorary Life Member #28 - Wallerstein, Morton L. (Box 31, Folder 41)
  - Honorary Life Member #125 - Wheeler, E. Todd (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Honorary Life Member #183 - White, Gilbert F. (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Honorary Life Member #26 - Whittemore, Harlow O. (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Honorary Life Member #64 - Wiecking, E.H. (Box 31, Folder 45)
  - Honorary Life Member #143 - Winsor, Edward (Box 31, Folder 46)
  - Honorary Life Member #100 - Winston, Oliver C. (Box 31, Folder 47)
  - Honorary Life Member #161 - Wolbrink, Donald H. (Box 31, Folder 48)
  - Honorary Life Member #38 - Woiman, Abel (Box 31, Folder 49)
  - Honorary Life Member #175 - Wrigley, Robert L., Jr. (Box 31, Folder 50)
  - Honorary Life Member #189 - Zuber, Leo J. (Box 31, Folder 51)
  - Honorary Life Members - cards for currently active (A-C), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Honorary Life Members - currently active (D-G), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 53)
  - Honorary Life Members - currently active (H-J), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 54)
  - Honorary Life Members - currently active (L-O), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 55)
  - Honorary Life Members - currently active (P-S), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 56)
  - Honorary Life Members - currently active (T-Z), 1978 (Box 31, Folder 57)
  - Honorary Life Members - deceased, pre- 1978 (A-H) (Box 31, Folder 58)
  - Honorary Life Members -deceased pre- 1978 (H-W) (Box 31, Folder 59)
  - Early Planning Greats (Box 31, Folder 60)
  - Subseries 1. Deceased Honorary Life Members
    - Honorary Life Member #50 - Ameter, Fred W. (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - Honorary Life Member #39 - Augur, Tracy B. (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - Honorary Life Member #64 - Bigger, Frederick (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Honorary Life Member #101 - Belser, Karl J. (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Honorary Life Member #34 - Black, Russell Van Nest (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Honorary Life Member #59 - Bohn, Ernest J. (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - Honorary Life Member #35 - Bonner, J. Franklin (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - Honorary Life Member #79 - Brender, Peter E. (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - Honorary Life Member #6 - Buttenheim, Harold S. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Honorary Life Member #47 - Carlson, Floyd A. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Honorary Life Member #52 - DeBoer, S.R. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Honorary Life Member #7 - Elwood, Philip H. (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Honorary Life Member #56 - Eastman, Ray C. (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Honorary Life Member #29 - Cousineau, Aime (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Honorary Life Member #15 - Fellows, Perry (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Freeman, Harry D. (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Honorary Life Member #103 - Geissal, Philip (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Honorary Life Member #36 - Greenfield, Albert M. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Honorary Life Member (number unknown) - Griffith, Russell (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Honorary Life Member #16 - Hare, S. Herbert (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Honorary Life Member #150 - Henderson, Fred (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Honorary Life Member #55 - Herring, Frank W. (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Honorary Life Member #1 - Herrald, George H. (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Honorary Life Member #17 - Hiebel, Leonard (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Honorary Life Member #30 - Klaber, Eugene Henry (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Honorary Life Member #31 - Lewis, Harold M. (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Honorary Life Member #8 - Lohman, Karl B. (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Honorary Life Member #9 - Lommel, George E. (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Honorary Life Member #10 - Mayne, Gerhardt F. (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Honorary Life Member #41 - Middleton, Paul E. (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Honorary Life Member #98 - Modak, N.V. (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Honorary Life Member #48 - Nussbaumer, Newell L. (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Honorary Life Member #67 - Oppermann, Paul (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Honorary Life Member #43 - Pitkin, Francis A. (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Honorary Life Member #83 - Root, Irving C. (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Honorary Life Member #71 - Shaw, A.H.C. (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Honorary Life Member #32 - Simons, George W., Jr. (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Honorary Life Member #21 - Swan, Herbert S. (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Honorary Life Member #19 - Stanberry, Van Buren (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Honorary Life Member #27 - Stein, Clarence S. (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Honorary Life Member #22 - Van Cleef, Eugene (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Honorary Life Member #23 - Vinton, Warren (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Honorary Life Member #24 - Vogel, Joshua H. (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Honorary Life Member #12 - Walker, J. Alexander (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Honorary Life Member #73 - Weinberg, Robert C. (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Honorary Life Member #94 - Williams, Leslie (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Subseries 2. Biographical Data Regarding Deceased ASPO Members
    - ASPO members on whom no obituaries were published (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - ASPO member - Abrams, Charles (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - ASPO member - Armstrong, Donald J. (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - ASPO member - Aschman, Frederick T. (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - ASPO member - Aschman, Michael P. (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - ASPO member - Backhouse, William O. (Honorary Life Member) (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - ASPO member - Ball, Edward (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - ASPO member - Bartlett, Frederick P. (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - ASPO member - Barnes, Ralph M. (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - ASPO member - Baughman, M. Eugene (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - ASPO member - Bell, Frederick K. (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - ASPO member - Bolotin, Adrian L. (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - ASPO member - Boyd, James (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - ASPO member - Brown, A.O. (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - ASPO member - Brussat, William K. (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - ASPO member - Burlingham, Robert (Box 32, Folder 54)
    - ASPO member - Campbell, Thomas A. (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - ASPO member - Card, Raymond W.G. (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - ASPO member - Centeio, George F. (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - ASPO member - Clark, Frederick P. (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - ASPO member - Coronella, Emilio S. (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - ASPO member - Cruttenden, Charles H. (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - ASPO member - Darling, Philip (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - ASPO member - Denhart, Clarence H. (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - ASPO member - deNoble, Henry M. (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - ASPO member - Duffy, Charles (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - ASPO member - Dulaney, Paul S. (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - ASPO member - Eberhardt, Siegfried W. (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - ASPO member - Edmonds, Leland R. (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - ASPO member - Finberg, Irving W. (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - ASPO member - Foster, E. Stanton (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - ASPO member - Foster, Francis R. (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - ASPO member - Friedman, Edmund (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - ASPO member - Frissel, J. Martin (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - ASPO member - Geer, David S. (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - ASPO member - Gibbs, Donald A. (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - ASPO member - Collins, Walter K. (Box 23, Folder 75)
    - ASPO member - Guhl, The Rev. Howard F. (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - ASPO member - Harmon, Darrell V. (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - ASPO member - Harmon, Gabriel C. (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - ASPO member - Heisner, Larry R. (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - ASPO member - Herman, M. Justin (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - ASPO member - Hippenmeyer, Bill R. (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - ASPO member - Hollingsworth, D.M. (Box 32, Folder 82)
    - ASPO member - Houston, William A. (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - ASPO member - James, Harlean (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - ASPO member - Johnson, Hayden B. (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - ASPO member - Joroff, Samuel (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - ASPO member - Kelley, Wilfrid D. (Box 32, Folder 87)
    - ASPO member - Hollister, Kent (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - ASPO member - Klintworth, Ronald M. (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - ASPO member - Krebs, Otto S., Jr. (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - ASPO member - Lamberson, R. Lindsey (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - ASPO member - Lehtinen, Gustaf H. (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - ASPO member - Levy, Lew (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - ASPO member - Luckenbach, Owen A. (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - ASPO member - Mailey, H. (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - ASPO member - Martin, A.G. (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - ASPO member - Maslan, Ellick (Box 32, Folder 97)
    - ASPO member - McCrosky, Theodore T. (Box 32, Folder 98)
    - ASPO member - Myrvik, Ronald M. (Box 32, Folder 99)
    - ASPO member - Nichols, W.H. (Box 32, Folder 100)
    - ASPO member - Ollerman, Archie (Box 32, Folder 101)
    - ASPO member - Osborn, Lady (Margaret Paterson Robb Osborn) (Box 32, Folder 102)
    - ASPO member - Osborn, Fairfield (Box 32, Folder 103)
    - ASPO member - Palmer, C.F. (Box 32, Folder 104)
    - ASPO member - Patterson, Timothy (Box 32, Folder 105)
    - ASPO member - Pickholtz, Morris M. (Box 32, Folder 106)
    - ASPO member - Pritchard, Hobart O. (Box 32, Folder 107)
    - ASPO member - Rabinow, Barney (Box 32, Folder 108)
    - ASPO member - Riley, Russell (Box 32, Folder 109)
    - ASPO member - Read, Phil (Box 32, Folder 110)
    - ASPO member - Reardon, Leslie J. (Box 32, Folder 111)
    - ASPO member - Rockman, Maury (Box 32, Folder 112)
    - ASPO member - Schultz, Harold (Box 32, Folder 113)
    - ASPO member - Settle, Duane E. (Box 32, Folder 114)
    - ASPO member - Shattuck, I.S. (Box 32, Folder 115)
    - ASPO member - Silverman, Stephen G. (Box 32, Folder 116)
    - ASPO member - Singleton, Doyle (Box 32, Folder 117)
    - ASPO member - Sweeney, James G. (Box 32, Folder 118)
    - ASPO member - Tankel, Stanley B. (Box 32, Folder 119)
    - ASPO member - Taylor, Burton L. (Box 32, Folder 120)
    - ASPO member - Taylor, Harold C. (Box 32, Folder 121)
    - ASPO member - Terrett, Barbara (Box 32, Folder 122)
    - ASPO member - Warner, William C. (Box 32, Folder 123)
    - ASPO member - Wegg, Talbot (Box 32, Folder 124)
    - ASPO member - Wheaton, William L.C. (Box 32, Folder 125)
    - ASPO member - Whitnall, Brysis N. (Mrs.) (Box 32, Folder 126)
    - ASPO member - Whitnall, Gordon (Box 32, Folder 127)
    - ASPO member - Wiener, Paul Lester (Box 32, Folder 128)
    - ASPO member - Wildt, Robert R. (Box 32, Folder 129)
    - ASPO member - Wilson, Wayne H. (Box 32, Folder 130)
    - ASPO member - Zerrien, Kenneth E., Sr. (Box 32, Folder 131)
    - ASPO member - Zikan, Joseph (Box 32, Folder 132)
    - ASPO member - Zisman, Samuel B. (Box 32, Folder 133)
  - Subseries 3. The following folders of ASPO members were removed for processing during 1977-78
    - ASPO member - Ashworth, Irving F. (Box 32, Folder 134)
    - ASPO member - Bacon, Edmund N. (Box 32, Folder 135)
    - ASPO member - Bennett, F.P. (Box 32, Folder 136)
    - ASPO member - Blake, Eloise S. (Box 32, Folder 137)
    - ASPO member - Cunningham, Jonathan (Box 32, Folder 138)
    - ASPO member - Eliot, Charles W. (Honorary Life Member) (Box 32, Folder 139)
    - ASPO member - Grimm, Sergei N. (Honorary Life Member #113) (Box 32, Folder 140)
    - ASPO member - Hill, Carroll V. (Honorary Life Member #130) (Box 32, Folder 141)
    - ASPO member - Hutton, Donald W. (Box 32, Folder 142)
    - ASPO member - Linsky, Benjamin (Box 32, Folder 143)
    - ASPO member - Locke, Howard W. (Box 32, Folder 144)
    - ASPO member - Marsch, George (Honorary Life Member #160) (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - ASPO member - Mocine, Corwin (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - ASPO member - Moore, Henry C. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - ASPO member - Olson, Howard R. (Honorary Life Member #63) (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - ASPO member - Osborn, Sir Frederick J. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - ASPO member - Robbins, Ira S. (Honorary Life Member #68) (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - ASPO member - Rouse, James W. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - ASPO member - Walker, Robert A. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - ASPO member - Wilkens, Edward B. (Honorary Life Member #154) (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - ASPO member - Yarwood, George A. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Honorary Life Members in progress during ASPO-AIP merger, 1977-79 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Honorary Life Members in progress during ASPO-AIP merger, 1977-78 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Honorary Life Members eligible, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Honorary Life Members in progress, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Obituaries, 1974-79 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - ASPO vice-presidents, officers, past presidents, medal winners, etc. (Box 33, Folder 16-17)
  - Historical materials (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - 25 year membership lists (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Membership lists (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Honorary Life Member policy, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Honorary Life Member lists, policy, memos, etc. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Life Members - memos, etc., 1970-72 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Form letters (including drafts) (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Honorary Life Members - certificates (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Honorary Life Members - printer's information (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Series VII. ASPO files regarding the American Institute of Planners
  - American City Planning Institute, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - American City Planning Institute, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - American City Planning Institute (becomes AIP Jan. 28, 1939 ), 1939 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - AIP, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - AIP, 1941 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - AIP, 1945 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - AIP, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - AIP, 1947 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - AIP, 1948 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - AIP, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - AIP, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - AIP - California, 1950-51 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - AIP, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - AIP - Chicago, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - AIP, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - AIP - California, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 16-17)
  - AIP Constitution (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - AIP Roster, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - AIP/ASPO Joint Board (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - AIP - Aid to Minority Planning Students (AMPS), 1971 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - AIP/ASPO Soviet Exchange (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
  - AIP Awards (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - AIP Board of Examiners (Box 35, Folder 8-10)
  - AIP Boards and Committee lists (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - AIP Brochures (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - AIP By-laws (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - AIP California Planner Bulletin (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - AIP Chapters (Box 35, Folder 15-16)
  - AIP Chicago Metro Section (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - AIP Committees and Divisions (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - AIP Committee reports (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - AIP Committee - Ad hoc (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - AIP Committee - ASCE-AIP Joint Coop (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - AIP Committee - Church Planning (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - AIP Committee - Competitions (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - AIP Committee - Council Meeting (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - AIP Committee - Developing Country Informatin Exchange (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - AIP Committee - Evaluation of Chapter Function (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - AIP Committee - Information Systems (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - AIP Committee - Licensing and Registration (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - AIP Committee - Minority Affairs (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - AIP Committee - National Education Development (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - AIP Committee - Nominating (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - AIP Committee - Planners in Federal Government (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - AIP Committee - Planning Education (Box 35, Folder 33-34)
  - AIP Committee - Programs for Planning Students (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - AIP Committee - Publication Advisory (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - AIP Committee - Restatement of Purpose (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - AIP Committee - State Planning (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - AIP Committee - Status of Planners in Federal Government (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - AIP Committee - Urban Renewal Administration (URA) (Box 35, Folder 40-41)
  - AIP Conferences, 1969-73 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - AIP Conferences, 1974-78 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - AIP Consultant Advertising (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - AIP Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - AIP Departments (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - AIP Education (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - AIP Elections (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - AIP Ethics (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
  - AIP Evaluation (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - AIP Foundation (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - AIP Illinois Chapter and Verse (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - AIP Information System Department (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - AIP Journal (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - AIP Lobbying (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - AIP Membership (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - AIP National Staff (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - AIP Oral Examinations (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - AIP Organization Data, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 15-16)
  - AIP - Planner's Political Primer (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - AIP Planners Roll Call, 1973-1975 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - AIP Planning Education Department (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - AIP Foundation of America (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - AIP Policy and Programs (Box 36, Folder 21-25)
  - AIP Policy Statements (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - AIP Registration Policy (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - AIP Task Force (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - AIP Town Planning (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Analysis of AIP Work (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - AIP Bulletin, 1945-1949 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Practicing Planner, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Practicing Planner, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- Series VIII. ASPO files regarding Association of State Planning and Development Agencies
  - Association of State Planning and Development Agencies (ASPDA) News Letter, Vol. 1-2, 1946-1947 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - ASPDA News Letter, Vol. 3, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - ASPDA Newsletter, Vol. 4, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - ASPDA Newsletter, Vol. 5, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - ASPDA Articles of Organization, Board of Directors meetings, 1946-1949 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - ASPDA Board of Directors meetings, 1946-1949 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - ASPDA Board of Directors meetings, 1950-1951 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - ASPDA Board of Directors meetings, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - ASPDA Bulletins - masterfile, 1946-1950 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - ASPDA Bulletins - masterfile, 1951-1952 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - ASPDA Bulletins - masterfile, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - ASPDA reports, 1947-1951 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - ASPDA Quarterly Activities reports (southern states), 1948 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous reports, 1950-51 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - ASPDA directory, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Proceedings of the Second Annual ASPDA Conference, Cincinnati, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Proceedings of the Third Annual ASPDA Conference, Nashville, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Proceedings of the Fourth Annual ASPDA Conference, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Proceedings of the Fifth Annual ASPDA Conference, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Proceedings of the Sixth Annual ASPDA Conference (Vol. I), 1951 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Committee reports of the Sixth Annual ASPDA Conference (Vol. II), 1951 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Proceedings of the Seventh Annual ASPDA Conference, Minneapolis, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Proceedings of the Eighth Annual ASPDA Conference, Hartford, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - ASPDA material to members, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - ASPDA, 1948-1952 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - ASPDA, 1951-1952 (Box 37, Folder 26)